<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://tapedrop.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://tapedrop.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-03-04T09:27:43-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tapedrop</title><subtitle>Jekyll Theme made with Halfmoon</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Velvet Kove - Even Angels Get Lonely</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/03/velvet-cove.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Velvet Kove - Even Angels Get Lonely" /><published>2022-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-03-03T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/03/velvet-cove</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/03/velvet-cove.html">&lt;iframe style=&quot;border-radius:12px&quot; src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/1DOBTP79hr9OYUn7otEP4b?utm_source=generator&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;200&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; fullscreen; picture-in-picture&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Richmond, VA based singer, songwiter, and multimedia artist &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/Velvet_Kove/&quot;&gt;Velvet Kove&lt;/a&gt; just dropped her first self produced beat tape &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/album/1DOBTP79hr9OYUn7otEP4b?si=UcKlVjWGTOKWMCUmTxs8dg&quot;&gt;Even Angels Get Lonely&lt;/a&gt;. The 3 track tape starts with Boys Don’t Cry, an infectious dance beat laced with spacey chords and vocoder leads. The second track, New Balance, begins as an airy, indie R&amp;amp;B type beat, and then shifts to bouncy electronic bass drums and synth arps. On the final track, Can You Keep It Down, Velvet Kove jams on some 8-bit sounding patches over a heavy drum machine. It sounds like something out of a Sega Genesis game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The origin story of Velvet Kove shares similarities with Tapedrop’s. Both started in New Jersey on a 2012 MacBook Pro. While house/cat sitting for her VCU professor in NJ, Velvet Kove began to tinker with Logic on her old MacBook. Since then she has graduated to an iMac with Ableton, an Arturia Keystep and a Blue Mic. “I am a strict Ableton kinda gal” she stressed in our interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;St. Vincent was her inital musical inspiration, but now her ear is more on hyperpop acts like SOPHIE, 100 gecs and Charli XCX. “I want to mix that industrial, mechanical sound, but with more 80s influences. I’m really into Dua Lipa right now, obvously Lady Gaga - just all of the popstars that are like ‘okay we get it, they’re famous already’. But yeah, I just wanna be a popstar.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A big driver for Velvet Kove is increasing the representation of women in the production side of music. She cited that only three women have won a Grammy for Producer of the Year, and all three were for the classical category. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.billboard.com/music/awards/women-record-producers-women-film-directors-awards-1235018826/&quot;&gt;A woman has never won a non-classical Grammy for Producer of the Year&lt;/a&gt;. Maybe one day Velvet Kove will change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even Angels Get Lonely and the rest of Velvet Kove’s discography are available on all the major streaming platforms. Check out her &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com?artist=i62qEXgvUpdZeukomqe8wrHvUr63&quot;&gt;Tapedrop Artist Card&lt;/a&gt; for links.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Tapedrop</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/velvet-kove.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/velvet-kove.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Dark World @ The Meat Locker</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/02/dark-world.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dark World @ The Meat Locker" /><published>2022-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-03-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/02/dark-world</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2022/03/02/dark-world.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/darkworld.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;meat locker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Friday, March 5th, Dark World co-founder and artist, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/djlucas413/?hl=en&quot;&gt;DJ Lucas&lt;/a&gt;, will be performing at the landmark venue in Montclair, NJ, along with appearances by Papa2oo4, Big Ovee, TrippythaKid, 89 The Brainchild, Subjxct5.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the last decade, DJ and his collaborators of the independent record label, Dark World, have brought lyrical and musical prowess, humor, and authenticity to the internet from deep in the woods of western Massachusetts. Their unique style is best showcased through the vast collection of raw, nostalgia-laced music videos on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/c/DARKWORLDMA/featured&quot;&gt;Dark World YouTube channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a 2017 interview on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fDbdPDl-m3E&quot;&gt;No Jumper podcast&lt;/a&gt;, DJ Lucas explains, “Dark World is just a thing. It just exists by itself.” At first glance, it may seem like a group of friends just having fun creating witty and self-aware music - and at its core, that’s what it is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But at the same time it goes much deeper than that. The group values genuine artistic expression. They make the process about having fun and learning, which yields unique and creative music that a diverse audience can identify with. For these reasons, Dark World has grown an almost cult-like following.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Dark World’s MO is repping small towns,’ said Lucas on No Jumper. The group recognizes that authenticity comes from loving what you do and having fun with your friends along the way. Coming from a small town, DJ can see himself in every aspiring artist with similar roots and is living proof that a balance exists between working hard and having fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the No Jumper interview, the host Adam Grandmaison put it best, “I think music industry people and fans of the culture would almost think it’s cooler to see a Dark World basement show with a 100 kids there freaking the fuck out.” On Friday, March 5th at the Meatlocker, that’s exactly what’s to be expected.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something special happens in the damp, poorly lit basement venues of small towns. Movements are born, trends and new cultures are created, and friendships are sparked. They are an active organism within the community that molds those who venture into the Dark World.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Doors open at 8:30pm at the Meatlocker in Montclair, New Jersey with a $10 entry fee.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find more from DJ Lucas and Dark World on their &lt;a href=&quot;https://darkworld.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Bandcamp&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/c/DARKWORLDMA/featured&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sam Mitchell</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/darkworld.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/darkworld.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Artist Spotlight&amp;amp;#58 Police Touch Museum</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2022/02/11/police-touch-museum.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Artist Spotlight&amp;amp;#58 Police Touch Museum" /><published>2022-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2022/02/11/police-touch-museum</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2022/02/11/police-touch-museum.html">&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nic_e977PAw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike Parry is a powerhouse in the Philly and Jersey music scenes. Many know him as the lead singer and guitarist for &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com?artist=SVXXY6D1XpW6nGqN9eOnniHYx7E2&quot;&gt;The Dead Flowers&lt;/a&gt;, a classic rock inspired staple known for their energetic performances. But when he’s not rock n’ rolling, Parry is working on his own project: &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com?artist=TX2QpeRBhiagnasSBDNGddOK7q73&quot;&gt;Police Touch Museum&lt;/a&gt;. Under this moniker, Parry delves into a modern indie rock, singer songwriter sound, citing influences such as Beck, John Mayer, the Shins, and The Beatles for his first single &lt;a href=&quot;https://policetouchmuseum.bandcamp.com/track/cut-myself-from-you&quot;&gt;Cut Myself From You&lt;/a&gt;. For current influences, Mike said “Lately I’ve been drawing inspiration from more modern artists like Cavetown and Pinegrove, but I prefer to keep the project’s sound as fluid as possible.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike started making and releasing music under Police Touch Museum because he wanted to explore a different side of his songwriting capabilities. “I like writing music of all different styles, and I wanted to start a project that didn’t have any niche genre, where I could just put the best of whatever I’m working on in one place. Besides the rock n roll songs, I hoard those for The Dead Flowers. PTM is a relatively new project - roughly 1 and half years old. When I started, I bought myself all the entry-level recording gear and have been working with the same stuff ever since. Laptop, Audio Technica AT4040 mic, Scarlet Focusrite interface. I record all the tracks in my apartment in Philly, but see myself expanding to other studios in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond playing shows, Mike is an active patron of local music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m a big fan of the Philly music scene – venues like Franklin Music Hall, Union Transfer, The Troc (RIP) were a huge part of my childhood. Shout out to my friends and favorite local bands: Ugli, Breaklite and The Warhawks.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Police Touch Museum is streaming on all major platforms. Check out his &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com?artist=TX2QpeRBhiagnasSBDNGddOK7q73&quot;&gt;Tapedrop Artist Card&lt;/a&gt; for links.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Tapedrop</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nic_e977PAw</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/police-touch-museum.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/police-touch-museum.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Jake Custer - Pennsylvania Song</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/27/jake-custer.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jake Custer - Pennsylvania Song" /><published>2022-01-27T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-01-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/27/jake-custer</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/27/jake-custer.html">&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcr5mHc73Mg&amp;amp;lc=z22mhjkzqt22hj0mracdp432p0ffxu52beencmgh311w03c010c&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Connecticut based classic rocker, Jake Custer, dropped Pennsylvania Song this week. The title song on the two sided release is an ode to the mountains of Pennsylvania, where Jake vacations with his family. Jake took the opportunity to record dueling guitar solos on this track, effectively capturing the spirit of PA’s wild wonders. Side B is a cover of I’m Not Your Stepping Stone, which was originally performed by Paul Revere &amp;amp; The Raiders. The release was mastered by Terry Manning, who has worked with ZZ Top, Led Zeppelin, Otis Redding and Big Star.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve had the pleasure of playing music with Jake at his home studio. His walls are lined with classic guitars and basses, and his fully loaded pedal boards could only have been assembled by a true sound scientist. Jake told me about his humble beginnings in the world of music production:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I started making music in 2012 when my brothers began recording on their laptop. The only recording gear I had was a Rock Band USB microphone and the presets on GarageBand. I think my favorite part of recording during this period was the gear I was using. My drum kit didn’t even have a kick pedal, the snare rested on a recycling bin and the (broken) cymbals were hanging off of traffic cones. It straight up looked like an ‘instrument skin’ you could unlock in Guitar Hero or Rock Band.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jake’s biggest influences are apparent through his music. Classic rock of the 60s and 70s - The Beatles, Big Star, Electric Light Orchestra and The Beach Boys - inform his style and tone. Hints of modern psychedelic influences like Tame Impala can be heard in his recordings as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jake wanted to give a shoutout to his dad and mom for supporting his music dreams, his brothers for introducing him to music, his friends Logan, Paul, Mat, Scott, and Joss for helping however they can, and Terry Manning for sharing his expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pennsylvania Song is available now on all major streaming services. Check out his &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com?artist=fQuYikmL0OSk3aoebBvuvJoT16u2&quot;&gt;Tapedrop Artist Card&lt;/a&gt; for links.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lcr5mHc73Mg&amp;amp;lc=z22mhjkzqt22hj0mracdp432p0ffxu52beencmgh311w03c010c</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/jakecuster.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/jakecuster.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Discover Local Music with the Tapedrop App</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/01/tapedrop-app.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Discover Local Music with the Tapedrop App" /><published>2022-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2022-01-01T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/01/tapedrop-app</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2022/01/01/tapedrop-app.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/posts/tapedrop-app.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;app screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce Tapedrop, the app! Available on iOS and web.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tapedrop uses geolocation to connect artists with local music fans. How it works: Artists create a profile with their music links - Apple Music, Spotify, Bandcamp, SoundCloud, Instagram and YouTube. That profile then appears for users within the immediate area. Profiles can be added to a user’s library for later listening, and easily shared. Shareable ‘Artist Cards’ are designed specifically for use as ‘Link in Bio’ pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Create your artist profile or start discovering new bands now at &lt;a href=&quot;https://app.tapedrop.com&quot;&gt;app.tapedrop.com&lt;/a&gt; or download the iOS app from &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/tapedrop/id1595625980&quot;&gt;the App Store&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For support, email support@tapedrop.com.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/tapedrop-app-card.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/tapedrop-app-card.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Privacy Policy</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2021/11/15/privacy-policy.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Privacy Policy" /><published>2021-11-15T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-11-15T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2021/11/15/privacy-policy</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2021/11/15/privacy-policy.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tapedrop built the Tapedrop app as a Free app. This SERVICE is provided by Tapedrop at no cost and is intended for use as is.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Tapedrop unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Information Collection and Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to Email, Images, Media Links. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics&quot;&gt;Google Analytics for Firebase&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://firebase.google.com/support/privacy/&quot;&gt;Firebase Crashlytics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Log Data&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in a case of an error in the app we collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cookies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent to your browser from the websites that you visit and are stored on your device’s internal memory.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However, the app may use third party code and libraries that use “cookies” to collect information and improve their services. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of this Service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Service Providers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To facilitate our Service;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To provide the Service on our behalf;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To perform Service-related services; or&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Links to Other Sites&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Children’s Privacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 years of age. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Changes to This Privacy Policy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This policy is effective as of 2021-11-16&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at support@tapedrop.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This privacy policy page was created at &lt;a href=&quot;https://privacypolicytemplate.net&quot;&gt;privacypolicytemplate.net&lt;/a&gt; and modified/generated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://app-privacy-policy-generator.nisrulz.com/&quot;&gt;App Privacy Policy Generator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><summary type="html">Privacy Policy</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/tapedrop-app.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/tapedrop-app.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Morgul Blade - A Last Waltz of Gevaudan</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2021/09/16/morgul-blade-music-video.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Morgul Blade - A Last Waltz of Gevaudan" /><published>2021-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-09-16T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2021/09/16/morgul-blade-music-video</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2021/09/16/morgul-blade-music-video.html">&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S-cOPiwlEKg&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Philadelphia-based metal band &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/morgul_blade_hm/&quot;&gt;Morgul Blade&lt;/a&gt; released their first music video this month. Produced by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/ritual_video/&quot;&gt;Ritual Video&lt;/a&gt;, it is animated in the style of an 8-bit side scroller. The story follows a group of swordsman hunting down a dangerous &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Beast_of_G%C3%A9vaudan&quot;&gt;beast of Gevaudan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video was released by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCc2JA2RL-97zdWNz71zg0PA&quot;&gt;No Remorse Records&lt;/a&gt;, who signed the band after their first tape, &lt;a href=&quot;https://morgulblade.bandcamp.com/releases&quot;&gt;Harbingers of Power and the World’s End&lt;/a&gt;, gained a loyal following on bandcamp.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I reached out to Lord Klauf, Morgul’s front man, to ask him about the band’s sudden success:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“It was very humbling. I initially started this project to just be a hobby to keep myself from watching too much tv and video games, never in a million years thought it would grow into an international label deal and potentially international tour next year.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also asked for three bands to check out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://malokarpatan.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Malokarpatan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“Slavic blackened heavy metal with excellent worldbuilding and strong melodic hooks”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://torpornoise.bandcamp.com/music&quot;&gt;Torpor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“Polish 3-piece that plays Black Metal in the 2nd wave style with heavy metal overtones”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blackmagicnorway.bandcamp.com/album/wizards-spell-2&quot;&gt;Black Magic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“Evil heavy metal in the vein of ‘Show No Mercy’ era Slayer… Riffs for fucking days”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A Last Waltz of Gevaudan was recorded at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.redwaterrecording.com/&quot;&gt;Red Water Recording&lt;/a&gt; in South Philly, along with the rest of Morgul Blades upcoming full length album “Fell Sorcery Abounds”, out by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/noremorserecords/&quot;&gt;No Remorse Records&lt;/a&gt; on November 26, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S-cOPiwlEKg</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/morgul_blade_video.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/morgul_blade_video.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">NYCL Kai drops “Bodies”</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYCL Kai drops “Bodies”" /><published>2021-04-05T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies.html">&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmedai0p95s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NYCL Kai just dropped his new single “Bodies” along with a neck-breaking Music Videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directed and shot by Connor Bewighouse (aka Pinkeeout) the video captures the high energy and euphoria of being enveloped in a mosh pit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kai goes absolutely off, back flipping into a crowd and moshing into a smashing finale you do not want to miss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/nycl_kai/&quot;&gt;NYCL Kai&lt;/a&gt; and his new apparel brand &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/newyorkcity.locals/&quot;&gt;NYCL&lt;/a&gt; (New York City Locals).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sam Mitchell</name></author><summary type="html">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmedai0p95s</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">For My Valentine &amp;lt;3</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2021/02/11/valentine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For My Valentine &amp;lt;3" /><published>2021-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2021/02/11/valentine</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2021/02/11/valentine.html">&lt;p&gt;Lyrics:
Hey
Let’s just stay in today
On this cold February day
All I need is your warm heart
And when
All the snow dries up
And your folks can come up
We’ll have a picnic up on a hill
And we’ll canoe on the lagoon
And look up at the moon
And I’ll kiss your tattoos, on your shoulder
Again and again&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><summary type="html">Lyrics: Hey Let’s just stay in today On this cold February day All I need is your warm heart And when All the snow dries up And your folks can come up We’ll have a picnic up on a hill And we’ll canoe on the lagoon And look up at the moon And I’ll kiss your tattoos, on your shoulder Again and again</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Christmas at the Stone Pony</title><link href="https://tapedrop.com/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christmas at the Stone Pony" /><published>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://tapedrop.com/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tapedrop.com/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/CSeKfstUEyE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Tis the season to rock n’ roll! In celebration of Christmas 2020, John Carr and his band &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Count Josephine&lt;/a&gt; took to the stage at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stoneponyonline.com/&quot;&gt;The Stone Pony&lt;/a&gt; to perform their Holiday single &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/track/christmas-comes-once-a-year-live-at-the-stone-pony-2020&quot;&gt;Christmas Comes Once A Year&lt;/a&gt;. With the help of our crew at Tapedrop, the performance was released on video in the style of a made-for-TV Christmas Special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The song was written by John Carr and performed in true Jersey Shore style, featuring a classic four-chord rhythm, Springsteen-esque bells, and a wailing saxophone solo. It was a heartfelt tribute to The Stone Pony and the Asbury Park tradition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope this special performance will be a bright spot in a Holiday Season that will be tough for so many of us. For more Count Josephine give them a visit on &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Bandcamp&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/countjosephineband1112&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCoronFr4AdGAaEMsZEmL6Yw&quot;&gt;Youtube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Live Sessions" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/CSeKfstUEyE</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tapedrop.com/stonepony.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://tapedrop.com/stonepony.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>