<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-08-30T10:14:12-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Tapedrop</title><subtitle>Jekyll Theme made with Halfmoon</subtitle><entry><title type="html">NYCL Kai drops “Bodies”</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="NYCL Kai drops “Bodies”" /><published>2021-04-05T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2021-04-05T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/04/05/nycl-kai-drops-bodies.html">&lt;p&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmedai0p95s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NYCL Kai just dropped his new single “Bodies” along with a neck-breaking Music Videos.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directed and shot by Connor Bewighouse (aka Pinkeeout) the video captures the high energy and euphoria of being enveloped in a mosh pit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kai goes absolutely off, back flipping into a crowd and moshing into a smashing finale you do not want to miss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to check out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/nycl_kai/&quot;&gt;NYCL Kai&lt;/a&gt; and his new apparel brand &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/newyorkcity.locals/&quot;&gt;NYCL&lt;/a&gt; (New York City Locals).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sam Mitchell</name></author><summary type="html">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmedai0p95s</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">For My Valentine &amp;lt;3</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/02/11/valentine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="For My Valentine &amp;lt;3" /><published>2021-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2021-02-11T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/02/11/valentine</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2021/02/11/valentine.html">&lt;p&gt;Lyrics:
Hey
Let’s just stay in today
On this cold February day
All I need is your warm heart
And when
All the snow dries up
And your folks can come up
We’ll have a picnic up on a hill
And we’ll canoe on the lagoon
And look up at the moon
And I’ll kiss your tattoos, on your shoulder
Again and again&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><summary type="html">Lyrics: Hey Let’s just stay in today On this cold February day All I need is your warm heart And when All the snow dries up And your folks can come up We’ll have a picnic up on a hill And we’ll canoe on the lagoon And look up at the moon And I’ll kiss your tattoos, on your shoulder Again and again</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Christmas at the Stone Pony</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Christmas at the Stone Pony" /><published>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/christmas-at-the-stone-pony.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/CSeKfstUEyE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;‘Tis the season to rock n’ roll! In celebration of Christmas 2020, John Carr and his band &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Count Josephine&lt;/a&gt; took to the stage at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stoneponyonline.com/&quot;&gt;The Stone Pony&lt;/a&gt; to perform their Holiday single &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/track/christmas-comes-once-a-year-live-at-the-stone-pony-2020&quot;&gt;Christmas Comes Once A Year&lt;/a&gt;. With the help of our crew at Tapedrop, the performance was released on video in the style of a made-for-TV Christmas Special.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The song was written by John Carr and performed in true Jersey Shore style, featuring a classic four-chord rhythm, Springsteen-esque bells, and a wailing saxophone solo. It was a heartfelt tribute to The Stone Pony and the Asbury Park tradition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope this special performance will be a bright spot in a Holiday Season that will be tough for so many of us. For more Count Josephine give them a visit on &lt;a href=&quot;https://thecountjosephineband.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Bandcamp&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/countjosephineband1112&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCoronFr4AdGAaEMsZEmL6Yw&quot;&gt;Youtube&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Live Sessions" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/CSeKfstUEyE</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/stonepony.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/stonepony.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Barney Cortez Debuts New Music Aboard Old School Bus</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/bad-company.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Barney Cortez Debuts New Music Aboard Old School Bus" /><published>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-12-07T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/bad-company</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/12/07/bad-company.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/KScTZc0j5hc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Somewhere along the Delaware River in a vacant lot in Camden, New Jersey, &lt;a href=&quot;https://linktree.com/barneycortez/&quot;&gt;Barney Cortez&lt;/a&gt; climbed aboard a retired school bus to debut his new music to the world. The song, &lt;a href=&quot;https://barneycortez.bandcamp.com/track/bad-company&quot;&gt;Bad Company&lt;/a&gt;, is the third track of Barney’s new EP, &lt;a href=&quot;https://barneycortez.bandcamp.com/album/drive-thru-heart&quot;&gt;Drive Thru Heart&lt;/a&gt;. Barney showcases his songwriting talents in this lyrical collection of tunes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The school bus and lot were provided by the eccentric guitar designer and artist, Phil Smith of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goldfinchgeetars.com/&quot;&gt;Goldfinch Guitars&lt;/a&gt;. Phil and Alyssa Ritchie, the hooded muse of the video, were in the process of converting the bus for a cross country road trip at the time of the shoot. Also joining the cast is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/aliawan.wav/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Ali Awan&lt;/a&gt;, a fellow Philly musician. The video was shot and edited by our very own &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/roldyclark/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Roldy Clark&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow and support Barney Cortez on &lt;a href=&quot;https://barneycortez.bandcamp.com/&quot;&gt;Bandcamp&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/barney.cortez/?hl=en&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, and stream &lt;a href=&quot;http://hyperurl.co/4pxfk2&quot;&gt;Drive Thru Heart&lt;/a&gt; - available on all major streaming platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Music Videos" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/KScTZc0j5hc</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/barney-bus.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/barney-bus.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Close Cash ‘Love or Lust’ Q&amp;amp;A</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/30/close-cash-love-or-lust.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Close Cash ‘Love or Lust’ Q&amp;amp;A" /><published>2020-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-30T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/30/close-cash-love-or-lust</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/30/close-cash-love-or-lust.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/sPD24QvK2Tc&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: What’s your origin story?
A: My life story is pretty crazy, born of Liberian descent, the first generation in my family to be born and raised in the US. My mother put me onto music early through Piano in the 2nd grade. I really wanted to do Karate but she signed me up for Piano anyway. It wasn’t until the 6th grade when I was introduced to actually making raps. Going to the homie Kenan’s house after school with Marcus Gray and Jordan Dash. We would just spend hours listening to beats on cassette tapes, writing and rapping to em. So you can say I’ve been rapping for about 15 years. Professionally? Around 2 to 3 years. What took me so long was coming to terms with the fact that this actually what I was born to do. Had to fight my family, peers, and myself to get to this point. Just glad I didn’t give up forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: How has your music and persona evolved over time?
A: Definitely has gotten darker over time. I think that is just a natural progression for the type of person I am in accordance to the situations I put myself into. I am a creature of the night life so everything that comes with it has made it’s way into my music. There’s a lot of fun but a lot of what comes in the night is dark. Lust for women, getting intoxicated, longing to feel something but searching for it in all the wrong places. That’s my vibe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q: What is your favorite venue to perform?
A: Pink Sotano was easily my favorite venue to perform at because of how intimate the performances actually are. It’s wild to think how much history has passed through that studio. So many legendary parties were held there as well. If you’re really in the Philly underground scene, you know how lit Pink Sotano was to everyone’s movement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q. What artists are you most inspired by?
A: OG wise? Ye easily. Doesn’t get better than that. Us both being Gemini’s with our birthdays a week apart. His video for Diamonds From Sierra Leone was the first Music Videos I ever watched that made me actually want to start doing music for real. From how he has been able to re-create himself on every project, revolutionize the sound, and stand on what he believes in regardless of who has to say anything about it. Ye is the best man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q. How do you feel about the independent rap scene in Philly?
A: It’s dope and a lot of individuals have been working super hard to make improvements to it. I think right now it’s at an all-time high again. I know there was an era before us that was super lit and the vibe I get from everyone is that it’s heading in that direction again. I notice a lot more unity in the scene compared to when I first started coming around and it is definitely dope to see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Q. Anyone you want to plug?
A: First off my aces, Hashland and MYKA. Both super lit artists I fuck with their music heavy. Hashland really be talking his shit for real on tracks and he be making most of his beats which is super fire to me. He also does all his own mixing and mastering. He’s helped me to learn a ton and elevate my sound crazy. Really my brother for life. Same with MYKA, he has taught me a lot about myself and shown me things I never would’ve recognized without crossing paths with him. Together we form a supergroup called TIL-3 and just seeing how we’re all moving individually, it’s gonna be dope to be on top with my brothers soon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/sPD24QvK2Tc</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/closecash.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/closecash.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Dead Flowers @ Tapedrop Live</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/14/the-dead-flowers-tapedrop-live.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Dead Flowers @ Tapedrop Live" /><published>2020-05-14T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-14T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/14/the-dead-flowers-tapedrop-live</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/05/14/the-dead-flowers-tapedrop-live.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/edQVG6EDV5c?list=PL8Zvz7lKR0wRbMo7EzALfpjxqvIgrRQjr&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Long ago, all the way back in the simpler times of February, The Dead Flowers teamed up with Tapedrop for a live session at the Cropwell Friends Meeting House in Marlton, NJ. The audio was engineered by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/connorpriest/&quot;&gt;Connor Priest&lt;/a&gt; with microphones provided by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gradwellhouse.com/&quot;&gt;Gradwell House Recording&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dead Flowers are a classic rock n’ roll band heavily inspired by The Rolling Stones. We talked to Zachary Tyler, the band’s lead guitarist, and he gave us the origin story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“We all met at Rutgers and started the band in 2015. I met John at the liquor store we both worked at in the summer and we both wanted to be the next Rolling Stones. From there, the jams began. We recruited Stephen, our keyboard player in 2018 who helped us further develop our sound with his music theory background and innovative playing.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Flowers are known for their high energy shows. They consistently manage to pack the house thanks to their showmanship. A few years ago they won the battle of the bands at the famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.stoneponyonline.com/&quot;&gt;Stone Pony&lt;/a&gt; in Asbury Park. Zach told us about that night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’d say our craziest show was when we won the battle of the bands. From ripping solos with blood on my face and having the crowd hold me up while I shred, it was the perfect mix of energy and excitement that helped us not only put on a great show, but helped us win the whole competition.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We asked Zach what the band’s biggest influences were, expecting the Rolling Stones, The Grateful Dead - but his response was much more wholesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Aside from the obvious influences, I think our biggest influences are each other. We learn and push each other to the best we can be, and I think that is equally important as all the greats who came before us.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dead Flowers are a blast to see live and we’re saddened that it may be awhile before their next gig - but thankfully we have this taped session to hold us over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to The Dead Flowers on &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/49vDQ8UzYcmeyMnnuVxtF3?si=SGHiZArJSAWZMSAvhgaIpg&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/artist/the-dead-flowers/id370300049?ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Music&lt;/a&gt; and follow them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/thedead_flowers/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/thedeadflowersnj/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Live Sessions" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/edQVG6EDV5c?list=PL8Zvz7lKR0wRbMo7EzALfpjxqvIgrRQjr</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/deadflowers.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/deadflowers.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Broadcast News Debut EP</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/04/12/broadcastnewsep.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Broadcast News Debut EP" /><published>2020-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-04-12T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/04/12/broadcastnewsep</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/04/12/broadcastnewsep.html">&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/3RjOxlGMzlDM4opRmYnKJT&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; height=&quot;210px&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowtransparency=&quot;true&quot; allow=&quot;encrypted-media&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Broadcast News released their debut EP on Good Friday after months of crafting in the studio. The 4 song record, running about 22 minutes long, was recorded at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.truelevelstudio.com/&quot;&gt;True Level Studio&lt;/a&gt; in Blackwood, NJ and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gradwellhouse.com/&quot;&gt;Gradwell House Recording&lt;/a&gt; in Haddon Heights, NJ. Adam Ackerman produced the EP with Tom Conran mixing and engineering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/tapedrop-blog/assets/images/posts/evan-piano.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;evan playing piano&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The band used some experimental techniques to craft their unique sounds. As pictured above, multi-instrumentalist Evan McCullough played grand piano over a guitar amp to achieve sympathetic resonance. The antique pump organ behind him was used in a few tracks. Adam, the producer, played vibraphone on Two Balloons and Tom recorded himself jingling his car keys around the studio for ambience. The band achieved many otherwordly sounds through synths like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.behringer.com/Categories/Behringer/Keyboards/Synthesizers-and-Samplers/DEEPMIND-12/p/P0AC5&quot;&gt;DeepMind&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.arturia.com/products/hardware-synths/microfreak/overview&quot;&gt;MicroFreak&lt;/a&gt;, and guitar pedals like the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.walrusaudio.com/products/julia-analog-chorus-vibrato-v2&quot;&gt;Walrus Julia&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://carolineguitar.com/product/meteore/&quot;&gt;Caroline Météore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Riding on top of this finely crafted production are the dark, crooning vocals of Aiden Lynch. Aiden sings of love and disillusionment through expressive vibrato over psychedelic harmonies. His emotional scope fluctuates from pain filled refrains like “Why don’t you love me?” to romantic nostalgia in Two Balloons: “We sat outside and watched the sky drift underneath our hanging feet. We talked all day and then at night I dream of you and you dream of me”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brenden Detwiler’s drumming lays the foundation with in-the-pocket grooves underneath Reid Howard’s sliding basslines and Alec Nolan’s heavily effected rhythm guitar. The album is a melting pot of genres, most prominently shoegaze and psychedelic rock. The 8 minute closer ‘I Like Your Planet’ starts as what feels like a krautrock track and abruptly transitions to a heavy prog breakdown to finish out the record.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listen to the EP on all major &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/album/3RjOxlGMzlDM4opRmYnKJT?si=FNJ1ygZJTlK7iW5CIsPW9w&quot;&gt;streaming platforms&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7LLaM8e3dIg&amp;amp;list=OLAK5uy_m_H_6MdIKlG8ueNmAvFZQonHHf-ezdwxA&quot;&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt;, and follow Broadcast News on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/bcastnews/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/bcastnews&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; to keep up with the band.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Articles" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/broadcastnews.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/broadcastnews.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Jeef - Block Your Number</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/03/26/jeef.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jeef - Block Your Number" /><published>2020-03-26T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-03-26T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/03/26/jeef</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/03/26/jeef.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/amafYtdBBUE&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jeff Dicken, also known as Jeef, is a singer, rapper and songwriter from Marlton, New Jersey. According to his &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/official_jeef&quot;&gt;Twitter bio&lt;/a&gt;, he is also ‘your mom’s favorite artist’. His debut album &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/album/3PGYwTsIIEMloZmhsbWbNW&quot;&gt;Songs Not About My X’s&lt;/a&gt; features bedroom pop tracks heavy in vintage synths and lovesick lyrics that are definitely not about his ex girlfriends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tapedrop teamed up with Jeef to produce the Music Videos for his song &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/jeef4/block-your-number?in=jeef4/sets/songs-not-about-my-xs-an-ep&quot;&gt;Block Your Number&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;https://harryherskowitz.com&quot;&gt;Harry Herskowitz&lt;/a&gt; directed the video which was shot at Cropwell Friends Meeting House in Marlton. The duotone, pink and blue lighting and bright red rotary phone shape the 80s outrun aesthetic, matching the song’s synthwave instrumentals. Jeef sings his woes to the unseen caller on the other end of the line, confessing his inner struggle to cut contact entirely - all while dancing and twirling around the old school phone cord.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The video is a big step forward for the young artist, who has already gained a loyal following through his relatable social media persona.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;1 retweet = 1 hug after quarantines over &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.co/LUJjXQZ62F&quot;&gt;pic.twitter.com/LUJjXQZ62F&lt;/a&gt; &amp;gt; — Jeef (@official_jeef) &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/official_jeef/status/1242485262560759808?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw&quot;&gt;March 24, 2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow Jeef on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/official_jeef&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/official.jeef/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; to keep up with new releases and listen to Songs Not About My X’s on &lt;a href=&quot;https://soundcloud.com/jeef4&quot;&gt;SoundCloud&lt;/a&gt; and all major &lt;a href=&quot;https://music.apple.com/us/album/songs-not-about-my-xs-ep/1500999685&quot;&gt;streaming platforms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Music Videos" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/amafYtdBBUE</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/jeef.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/jeef.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Zoloft Zombie @ Tapedrop Live</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/02/13/zoloftzombie.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Zoloft Zombie @ Tapedrop Live" /><published>2020-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-02-13T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/02/13/zoloftzombie</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/02/13/zoloftzombie.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/qFg_Rlmp7VQ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoloft Zombie, 24, is a rapper, producer, and spoken word poet from Trenton, New Jersey. Zoloft Zombie, or Zoza, has been creating music since 2014, gaining notoriety in the basement show scene of Rutgers University as well as on Rutgers’ internationally ranking spoken word poetry team, Lucid Language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aside from the occasional collaboration, Zoza produces all of his beats himself. The dark and dissonant tone of his music is accompanied by lyrics focusing on social activism and advocacy ranging from racial inequality to stigmas against mental health. Zoza describes his music as a vehicle of expression that has aided him in coping with depression, anxiety, and substance dependence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Zoza hopes to inspire people to turn their darkness and pain outward through creativity and use art as a therapeutic practice. “If you have something inside you, don’t procrastinate and get it out there.” These are words that Zoza lives by as he actively creates a platform for other artists to create and perform. Zoza hosts monthly basement shows at the venue appropriately named The Underwrld. Follow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/zoloftzombie/&quot;&gt;@zoloftzombie&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/the.undrwrld/&quot;&gt;@the.undrwrld&lt;/a&gt; for details on upcoming shows and listen to Zoza on major &lt;a href=&quot;https://open.spotify.com/artist/0X9FnK3mFNlru0T4PqyyBD&quot;&gt;streaming&lt;/a&gt; platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sam Mitchell</name></author><category term="Live Sessions" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/qFg_Rlmp7VQ</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/zoloft.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/zoloft.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Mr. Magine @ Tapedrop Live</title><link href="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/01/30/mr-magine.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mr. Magine @ Tapedrop Live" /><published>2020-01-30T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2020-01-30T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/01/30/mr-magine</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/2020/01/30/mr-magine.html">&lt;p&gt;https://youtu.be/ZyQviHddqNU&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mr. Magine, AKA Kyle Esler, is different than other new artists in today’s indie rap scene. His lyrical content discusses topics and ideas professed by modern spiritual teachers, from Alan Watts to his Shr fu Dr. John Lee. He raps from the front lines of what he calls the “war on consciousness.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By including the prefix “Mr.” in his stage name, Magine clearly declares his role as a teacher to the youth of today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Kids should be meditating in school and learning about the law of attraction, etc.” says Mr. Magine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Taking inspiration from artists like Tupac, Kid Cudi, and even Bon Iver, Mr. Magine’s raw and unapologetic album “Journey I: Entering the Cosmos” is less of a wake up call and more of a cold bucket of water to the face during a societally constructed coma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Magine’s singular goal and objective with his music is to accelerate the inevitable paradigm shift that this country, and the world, are bound for and deeply require. He raps about believing in the power of oneself, working on the tough philosophical questions that can only be confronted by turning awareness inward, and spreading love and compassion to all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the fact that Mr. Magine’s first album is called &lt;em&gt;Journey I&lt;/em&gt;, we can all look forward to the second musical installment of this young and hungry artist’s spiritually and culturally progressive perspective.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to listen to his latest album on major streaming platforms and follow him on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/mr.magine/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Mr.Magine/&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harry Herskowitz</name></author><category term="Music Videos" /><summary type="html">https://youtu.be/ZyQviHddqNU</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/magine.jpg" /><media:content medium="image" url="https://roldyclark.github.io/tapedrop-blog/magine.jpg" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" /></entry></feed>